nettwerk.com 2009-04-20

# Nettwerk

**Nettwerk Music Group Privacy Policy** Nettwerk Music Group and this site care about your privacy. This privacy policy tells you what information we collect at our web sites and how we use it. 

**What Information We Collect** There are many places at our sites where you can share your personal information with us, and where you can communicate with others. 

**Registration** Some of our sites give you the opportunity to register with us, and sometimes registration is required before certain site features can be used. Our registration forms may request your contact information (such as your name, email address, mailing address, etc.), demographic information (such as your country, gender, etc.), and profile data (such as your music preferences, entertainment practices, etc). You may be assigned a site username and/or password. For our internal purposes, we use this information to communicate with you and provide the services you have requested, and to provide a more personalized experience on our sites. For example, your registration may allow you to use and post to site message boards, create site profiles, etc. We use aggregate demographic and profile information about our audience in order to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or for industry reporting purposes. 

**Newsletters and Other Communications from Us** Our registered users and customers may receive newsletters or other email communications from our family of sites and record label, and we may also offer other users the opportunity to sign up to receive such information. When there is a separate sign-up for newsletters, we ask for contact information such as name and email address, and, occasionally, demographic and profile information. We use this information in the same manner as we use the contact information in the Registration process described above. We may offer our users the choice whether to receive mailings from others that we think will be of interest. Recipients of our mailings can unsubscribe by following instructions that may appear at the end of the email newsletter. Note that in order to keep our registered users informed about the operation of our services, we may send emails and announcements that are needed for the proper functioning and administration of our sites and service. 

**Communications with Us** We have features where you can submit information to us (such as when contacting us with a question or feedback). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better. 

**Communications with Friends** We may offer features where you can send information to others, such as e-cards or ’Tell A Friend’ featur. We will use the contact information you enter for your friends to send the email or e-card. 

**Interactive and Community Features** Our sites may offer interactive and community features, such as message boards, chat, email accounts, instant messaging, profiles, personal homepages, etc. All information posted or sent through these features may be publicly available, and you should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., user name, email address, phone number) through these features, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited communications from other people. Users’ posts may be publicly and/or internally associated with their profiles/screen-names. Users are solely responsible for the content of messages they post or send on public forums. 

**Contests, Sweepstakes and Surveys** We may also have contests, sweepstakes and surveys at our sites. When you enter or participate in them, we request contact information from you (such as your full name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number) and may also request demographic or profile information. We will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (for example, to contact you if you have won). We may also use the information to send you newsletters and other information we think may be of interest. Recipients of our mailings can unsubscribe by following instructions that may appear at the end of the email newsletter. Any personal information collected will be used by us and may be associated with registration information. We may share aggregate information with others. We may sometimes partner with sponsors in offering contests, sweepstakes or surveys, and may share (provide and receive) information with them. 

**Automatic Data Collection** Our web sites have features that automatically collect information from users to assist us in creating sites that honor our users’ preferences and serve their needs. 

Some of our sites use cookies, which are small data files containing information about the user that are stored on the user’s hard drive. Some cookies are used to make login to our sites easier (such as by remembering usernames and passwords. If users reject cookies, they may be limited in using some areas of our sites. Cookies can also enable us to track users’ movements and target their interests to enhance their experience at our sites. 

For our internal purposes, we may gather information such as the date, time, browser type, navigation history, and IP address of all visitors to our site(s). We use this information for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, and system administration, and to gather broad demographic information about our user base for aggregate use. 

**With Whom Your Information Is Shared** Information provided at Artist sites that we host or manage may be shared with that Artist, including their management, representatives, and any new label they may join. We may also share your information with others if you choose to let us do so, such as where we offer opt-out or opt-in choices. 

Other than as set forth in this policy, we do not share your personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our service to you, and which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Also, please be aware that Nettwerk Music Group, including all its business units, subsidiaries, affiliates and sites, entities into which our company may be merged, or entities to which any of our assets, products, sites or operations may be transferred, may obtain from us and be able to use your personal information. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. 

We may share (provide and receive) aggregate information, which is not personally identifiable, with others. This information may include demographic data such as the gender and/or geographic location of groups of users, but it will not include personal information (such as your name or email address). We use aggregate demographic information about our audience in order to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting purposes. 

**Choice** Our sites may provide you the opportunity to choose to receive communications from us or from third parties at the point where we request information about you. 

**Access** If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code), we endeavor to provide a way to correct or update that user’s personal data. Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions regarding making changes to your data. 

**Data Collection From Children** Nettwerk does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to Nettwerk. At many sites, we actively screen-out children from data collection and/or use of interactive or community features. We are committed to protecting children's privacy. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact our privacy officer at [currell@nettwerk.com](mailto:currell@nettwerk.com)

**Security** Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. We store your personal information securely, and use special procedures designed to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. 

**Links** We may provide links to non-Nettwerk Music Group sites. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users, and we advise you to check their privacy policies. 

**Privacy Policy Changes** We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this policy from time to time. 

**Contact** If you have any questions or complaints about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact our privacy officer: 

**Jason Currell <[currell@nettwerk.com](mailto:currell@nettwerk.com)>  
Nettwerk Music Group  
1650 West 2nd Ave.   
Vancouver B.C. V6J 4R3  
604-654-2929**
